Hey there, my friends. It's Tom with
Watchman River.
Early Sunday morning here by the river
in the middle of Connecticut. It is
September 6th,
2026. I want to start off reading some
scripture. I'm in God's promises for
your every need.
Little book that contains scripture.
What page am I on? I'm on 83. What to do
when you feel lonely? Let's read a few
of these, okay?
Hebrews 13:5, "Let your conduct be
without covetousness.
Be content with such things as you have.
For he himself has said, 'I will never
leave you nor forsake you.'"
I'll take an amen.
Thank you.
Let's go to Matthew 28:20, "Teaching
them to observe all things that I have
commanded you. And lo, I am with you
always, even to the end of the age.
Amen."
>> [clears throat and cough]
>> 1 Samuel 12:22,
"For the Lord will not forsake his
people
for his great name's sake, because it
has pleased the Lord to make you his
people."
Isaiah 41:10, one of my favorites, "Fear
not, for I am with you. Be not dismayed,
for I am your God. I will strengthen
you. Yes, I will help you. I will uphold
you with my righteous right hand."
Then the words of Jesus in John 14:18,
"I will not leave you orphans. I will
come to you."
>> [clears throat]
>> Excuse me. John 14, the first verse.
"Let not your heart be troubled. You
believe in God, believe also in me."
Deuteronomy 33:27,
"The eternal God is your refuge, and
underneath are the everlasting arms. He
will thrust out the enemy from before
you and will say, 'Destroy.'"
Wow. We serve a powerful God. Psalm
147:3, "He heals the brokenhearted and
binds up their wounds."
Let's go to Deuteronomy 4:31.
For the Lord your God is a merciful God.
He will not forsake you nor destroy you
nor forget the covenant of your fathers
which he swore to them.
Deuteronomy 31:6. Be strong and of good
courage. Do not fear nor be afraid of
them.
For the Lord your God, he is the one who
goes with you. He will not leave you nor
forsake you.
How many times somebody, this is trivia
cuz I don't know. How many times does it
say throughout the entire word of God,
he will not leave you nor forsake you?
Somebody look that up.
Let's go to Psalm 27:10. When my father
and my mother forsake me, then the Lord
will take care of me.
Isaiah 54:10.
For the mountains shall depart and the
hills be removed, but my kindness shall
not depart from you nor shall my
covenant of peace be removed, says the
Lord who has mercy on you.
1 Peter
chapter 5:7.
Casting all your care upon him for he
cares for you.
Let's do one more. Psalm 46, the first
verse.
God is our refuge and strength, a very
present help in trouble.
Beautiful [clears throat] scripture. How
are you guys today?
I hope you are doing well.
Sundays we don't cover the news or
anything like that. Sundays we have set
aside just to pray for each other.
And uh we've done this a long time and
many, many lives have been changed
through the prayers that are said
underneath these videos. So, we do a
much shorter video just to have a place
to put the comments
so that you can put your prayer requests
there and it doesn't matter if it's for
yourself or anyone else, you will be
prayed for
uh because I always ask that when you
leave your your prayer request,
don't just exit the building. If you
could just maybe look at a
few other comments and and pray for them
and reply and let them know you prayed
for them or thumb up their comment. And
they'll know they were prayed for. Um
it's just, you know, a wonderful thing
we do here, praying for each other. I I
really believe it's the most important
thing
we do here, you know, is prayer, you
know, talking to the one who sent his
only begotten son to
to save us, to rescue us, you know. So,
that's what we do here. And we're going
to do it till the first Sunday we're not
here.
And my goodness, that could be anytime,
you know. Every Sunday I come here, I
always think, could this be the last
Sunday? It could. It could. But I'm
going to say a prayer if you don't mind
and then we'll get busy, okay?
>> [clears throat and cough]
>> Father in heaven,
thank you.
I sit here in awe before you, Father,
because you are
you're so good.
You are a God,
the one and only most high God who is
full of mercy
and grace and truth.
And we need your mercy and your grace
and we love your truth.
We thank you that you sent your only
begotten son
because you were not willing that any
should perish, but that all should come
to repentance. That is so beautiful.
We will thank you forever and ever for
what you've done for us.
Father, I lift up the Watchman River
family to you, this little sliver of
your body,
of people that
>> [clears throat]
>> Excuse me, people that love you.
And I lift them up, Lord, in
in these last days, there's so
many things going on in this world.
People are having great financial
problems and
spiritual problems and relationship
problems and health
problems and I lift them up to you,
Lord, and say, "Can you do a mighty work
in their lives today? Show my brothers
and sisters your presence today
as you always do, but Lord, do that and
heal the ones with health problems and
prosper the ones who need
help in financial areas in their life
and
and show the presence your presence
to the ones who are having relationship
or spiritual problems, Lord.
I just trust that you're going to show
up in a mighty way. Lord, I pray for the
people around the world who are
they don't even know they're aching for
you, but they're aching for you, Lord.
Can you draw many
by your spirit this very day and save
many?
That's our prayer, Lord, to see many
more saved
because we know, Jesus, we know
you are coming soon.
And we want more and more people on the
ark.
One day soon, we will be face to face
with you, Jesus.
And we long for that day
as we also hurt for the ones who will be
left behind.
Oh, Lord.
Thank you so much for who you are.
Thank you. Draw many by your spirit. We
expect a mighty work today
because you are a saving God.
We don't have the power to save, Lord.
We can only spread your beautiful
gospel.
But save many today. We ask it in your
precious name, Jesus. Amen.
Okay, my friends. I almost forgot there
was a camera in my face.
>> [clears throat]
>> Um
What are you guys doing today? I hope
you have
good plans. Uh I am
heading off to church
today with my family and uh
and you you guys are the church, too,
because we all Church means people that
belong to the Lord.
It's not a building, right?
But, I am heading to a building today to
worship the most high God.
And uh
you know, it'll be good.
But, I hope you guys have a really good
day today. Hope you're blessed
with good food and
and family and
and uh
I love you guys. And if we're not
raptured today, and I think today's a
perfectly good day for the rapture, but
if not, God willing,
I will see you guys tomorrow. I love you
guys.
>> Oh, Jesus.
>> [music]
>> Savior.
Master.
>> [music]
>> Creator.
You're the alpha.
>> [music]
>> Omega.
You're the
>> [music]
>> king of
kings.